guide4moms.com 2017-02-02

# Privacy Policy - Guide 4 Moms

  * Survival Guide Media LLC (" **Survival Guide Media** ") operates guide4moms.com and may operate other websites. It is Survival Guide Media's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Survival Guide Media collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Survival Guide Media's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Survival Guide Media's visitors use its website. From time to time, Survival Guide Media may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Survival Guide Media also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on guide4moms.com blogs/sites. Survival Guide Media only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Survival Guide Media's websites choose to interact with Survival Guide Media in ways that require Survival Guide Media to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Survival Guide Media gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [guide4moms.com](http://www.guide4moms.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Survival Guide Media are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Survival Guide Media collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Survival Guide Media. Survival Guide Media does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Survival Guide Media may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Survival Guide Media may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Survival Guide Media does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Survival Guide Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Survival Guide Media's behalf or to provide services available at Survival Guide Media's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Survival Guide Media's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Survival Guide Media will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Survival Guide Media discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Survival Guide Media believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Survival Guide Media, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Survival Guide Media website and have supplied your email address, Survival Guide Media may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Survival Guide Media and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Survival Guide Media takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Survival Guide Media uses cookies to help Survival Guide Media identify and track visitors, their usage of Survival Guide Media website, and their website access preferences. Survival Guide Media visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Survival Guide Media's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Survival Guide Media's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Survival Guide Media, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Survival Guide Media goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Survival Guide Media may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Survival Guide Media and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Survival Guide Media may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Survival Guide Media's sole discretion. Survival Guide Media encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a guide4moms.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
